Okay, so we've proven that an input to a
function keeps its properties. So when
we input a string into this function, we
can trim and uppercase it. What that
means is that if we wrote a function, um
it could probably take another function
and call it because a function should
keep its properties when it's passed as
an input and a function has the
properties that you can call it. So
let's just see how that works. So let's
comment that out. And what I'm going to
do is I'm going to create a new function
and I'm going to say function um
alert
caller. Um and then I'm just going to
give it an input function.
Um is what I'm going to ask for as an
input. And then all I'm going to do is
I'm going to call the input function.
So
I'm going to use my alert caller and
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
pass in alert. So if this works, it
should take alert as an input function
and then it should call alert.
So let's save this and let's go here and
we get an empty alert box. Um if we
inspect our code and we put a breakpoint
on line 22
and we reload the page, it comes here
says alert caller. What are we passing
in? Well, the function called alert. If
we hit next, if we hover over input
function, it is a function called alert.
We hit next, it calls the alert and
we're done. So
now we know that a function can take a
function and call it. Why is this
helpful? Well, because it means that
someone can pass a function in and we
don't need to know what their function
is or what it's called. We can just take
it as an input and call it. And in the
next video, I'll demonstrate why you
might want to do